{
    "id": "9a8b8c42bd1b467dbf5933023909eb8f",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He didn’t work hard ……………………. he failed his exam.",
            "description": "So gives the effect. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "because",
                "as"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "859da880678b4c5ba238a4e2a9c269ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. had the hunter raised the gun, than the birds flew away.",
            "description": "The correct conjunction is no sooner ... than...",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "No sooner",
                "Hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a61e12a1e57645efa77c6db2fb88a669"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………… intelligent to be defeated.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ff86f174df94135a7c17cfb00850ee3"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. had she got the message when she started.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Hardly",
                "Scarcely",
                "No sooner"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e85b39a4ea9d4c6d9a74f1661a6be6bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… my children are employed, I have no financial difficulties.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "That",
                "Now",
                "Now that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ee4366f5187a48b0b1099ed27efff2c9"
        },
        {
            "question": "They still live in the house ………………………… was built by their grandfather.",
            "description": "Either which or that can refer to non-living things in identifying relative clauses. ",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "what",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "27783d928a654e84afaa5e9a30d53c83"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… he saw a dog, he threw stones at it.",
            "description": "Whenever means it doesn't matter when.",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "Whenever",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6475511135f84e88a43515402b32b5a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should neither see him …………………… call him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "nor",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3edc42a2c6d64612a0ee82fe707295f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… he is honest, everybody respects him.",
            "description": "All of these words indicate the reason for something. ",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "As",
                "Because",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "946dcd4dc49c40f4af6674d9610b39d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. my mother is a doctor, she knows how to dress a wound.",
            "description": "As indicates the reason.",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "So",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8b09dd6d27ea45c68a0e7343d6e660d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not be able to meet him ………………………. you arrive in time.",
            "description": "Unless is similar to if not. ",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if",
                "without"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "24516dea0d9c4ff98e5c951fceda2738"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… his health is poor, he attends his office regularly.",
            "description": "Although is similar to but it is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Although",
                "However",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5b2756cbe4854881895bbb279dc0c4bd"
        }
    ]
}